adsbridge.com 2015-09-14

# AdsBridge - Next generation tracker and landing page builder!

##  Overview 

Adsbridge Asia Limited (Hong Kong), trading as AdsBridge ("AdsBridge", "we", "us" or "our") is committed to protecting the privacy of personal information of identifiable individuals who visit the [www.adsbridge.com](http://adsbridge.com/) website (the "Site") and use the services available thereon (the "Services"). Amendments to this Privacy Policy will be posted to the Site and/or Services and will be effective when posted. Your continued use of the Services following the posting of any amendment to the Privacy Policy shall constitute your acceptance of such amendment. 

###  1\. Consent and Information Collection and Use 

When you join us as a user of our Services, we ask for personal information that will be used to activate your account, provide the Services to you, communicate with you about the status of your account, and for other purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. Your name, company name, address, telephone number, email address, credit card information and certain other information about you may be required by us to provide the Services or disclosed by you during your use of the Services. You will also be asked to create a private password, which will become part of your account information. 

By providing personal information to us and by retaining us to provide you with the Services, you voluntarily consent to the collection, use and disclosure of such personal information as specified in this Privacy Policy. Without limiting the foregoing, we may on occasion ask you to consent when we collect, use, or disclose your personal information in specific circumstances. Sometimes your consent will be implied through your conduct with us if the purpose of the collection, use or disclosure is obvious and you voluntarily provide the information. 

We may use your personal or account information for the following purposes: 

  * To provide the Services to you and to improve the quality of the Site and Services,
  * To provide information to you so that you may use the Site and Services more effectively,
  * To create, manage and control your account information, and to verify access rights to services and software,
  * To bill your account,
  * To communicate with you for the purpose of informing you of changes or additions to the Services, or of the availability of any service we provide,
  * To assess service levels, monitor traffic patterns and gauge popularity of different service options,
  * To carry out our marketing activities;
  * To enforce this Privacy Policy;
  * To respond to claims of any violation of our rights or those of any third parties;
  * To respond to your requests for customer service;
  * To protect the rights, property or personal safety of you, us, our users and the public; and as required or authorized by law.

We may occasionally communicate with you regarding our products, services, news and events. You have the option to not receive this information. We provide an opt-out function within all email communications of this nature, or will cease to communicate with you for this purpose if you contact us and tell us not to communicate this information to you. The only kind of these communications that you may not "opt-out" of are those required to communicate announcements related to the Services, including information specific to your account, planned Services suspensions and outages. We will attempt to minimize this type of communication to you. 

###  2\. Age of Consent 

We do not knowingly provide the Services to, and will not knowingly collect the personal information from anyone under the age of consent. 

###  3\. Rights to Your Information 

You have the right to access and edit your information at any time through the web interface provided as part of the Services. 

###  4\. Disclosure 

We will only share your information with third parties in accordance with your instructions or as necessary to provide you with a specific service or otherwise in accordance with applicable privacy legislation. As a general rule, we do not and will not sell, rent, share or disclose your personal information without first receiving your permission or as permitted in this Privacy Policy. 

###  5\. Aggregated Data 

We may also use your personal information to generate Aggregated Data for internal use and for sharing with others on a selective basis. "Aggregated Data" means records which have been stripped of information potentially identifying customers, landing pages or end-users, and which have been manipulated or combined to provide generalized, anonymous information. Your identity and personal information will be kept anonymous in Aggregated Data. 

###  6\. Links 

The Site may contain links to other sites and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of linked sites. Their privacy policies and practices differ from our policies and practices. 

###  7\. Cookies and Log Files 

We use cookies and log files to track user information. Cookies are small amounts of data that are transferred to your web browser by a web server and are stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to track which page variant a visitor has seen, to track if a visitor has clicked on a page variant, to monitor traffic patterns and to gauge popularity of service options. We will use this information to deliver relevant content and services to you. This also allows us to make sure that visitors see the landing page they expect to see if they return to the same web URL and it allows us to tell you how many people click on your landing pages. 

###  8\. Change of Ownership or Business Transition 

In the event of a change of ownership or other business transition, such as a merger, acquisition or sale of our assets, your information may be transferred in accordance with applicable privacy laws. 

###  9\. Security 

We will strive to prevent unauthorized access to your personal information, however, no data transmission over the Internet, by wireless device or over the air is guaranteed to be 100% secure. We will continue to enhance security procedures as new technologies and procedures become available. 

We strongly recommend that you do not disclose your password to anyone. If you forget your password, we will ask you for your ID and send you an email containing a link that will allow you to reset your password. 

Please remember that you control what personal information you provide while using the Services. Ultimately, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your identification, passwords and/or any personal information in your possession for the use of the Services. Always be careful and responsible regarding your personal information. We are not responsible for, and cannot control, the use by others of any information which you provide to them and you should use caution in selecting the personal information you provide to others through the Services. Similarly, we cannot assume any responsibility for the content of any personal information or other information which you receive from other users through the Services, and you release us from any and all liability in connection with the contents of any personal information or other information which you may receive using the Services. We cannot guarantee, or assume any responsibility for verifying, the accuracy of the personal information or other information provided by any third party. You release us from any and all liability in connection with the use of such personal information or other information of others. 

###  10\. Contact Us 

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please  contact us here.
